<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<catalog>
    <anime>
        <name>One Piece</name>
        <description>One Piece is the name the world gave to all the treasure gained by the 
        Pirate King Gol D. Roger. At least a portion of it once belonged to Joy Boy during 
        the Void Century. The treasure is said to be of unimaginable value, and is currently 
        located on the final island of the Grand Line: Laugh Tale.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/one piece-logo.jpg</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Jujutsu Kaisen</name>
        <description>Jujutsu Kaisen is the story of Yuji Itadori, an easygoing high school 
        student who joins the occult club at school. When they accidentally summon grotesque 
        creatures by messing with a cursed object, Itadori fights to save his friends' lives.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/jujutsu-logo.jpg</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Demon Slayer</name>
        <description>It is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Koyoharu Gotōge, 
        and it is about Tanjiro Kamado, a young boy who becomes a demon slayer after his family 
        is slaughtered and his younger sister Nezuko is turned into a demon.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/Demon-Slayer-Logo.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Naruto</name>
        <description>It tells the story of Naruto Uzumaki, a young ninja who seeks recognition 
        from his peers and dreams of becoming the Hokage, the leader of his village</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/naruto.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Slam Dunk</name>
        <description>The story follows Hanamichi Sakuragi, who falls in love with a girl named Haruko Akagi, 
        and decides to enter the Shohoku High School Basketball Team in order to attract her, as she is 
        already in love with another Shohoku player, Kaede Rukawa.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/slamdunk.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Bleach</name>
        <description>High school student Ichigo Kurosaki, who has the ability to see ghosts, gains soul 
        reaper powers from Rukia Kuchiki and sets out to save the world from "Hollows".</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/bleach.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Dragon Ball</name>
        <description>Dragon Ball tells the tale of a young warrior by the name of Son Goku, a young 
        peculiar boy with a tail who embarks on a quest to become stronger and learns of the Dragon Balls, 
        when, once all 7 are gathered, grant any wish of choice.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/dragonball.png</location>
    </anime>
</catalog>