<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>

<catalog>
    <anime>
        <name>One Piece</name>
        <description>One Piece is the name the world gave to all the treasure gained by the 
        Pirate King Gol D. Roger. At least a portion of it once belonged to Joy Boy during 
        the Void Century. The treasure is said to be of unimaginable value, and is currently 
        located on the final island of the Grand Line: Laugh Tale.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/one piece-logo.jpg</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Jujutsu Kaisen</name>
        <description>Jujutsu Kaisen is the story of Yuji Itadori, an easygoing high school 
        student who joins the occult club at school. When they accidentally summon grotesque 
        creatures by messing with a cursed object, Itadori fights to save his friends' lives.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/jujutsu-logo.jpg</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Demon Slayer</name>
        <description>It is a Japanese manga series written and illustrated by Koyoharu Gotōge, 
        and it is about Tanjiro Kamado, a young boy who becomes a demon slayer after his family 
        is slaughtered and his younger sister Nezuko is turned into a demon.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/Demon-Slayer-Logo.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Black Clover</name>
        <description>Set in a world where everyone is given the ability to use magic, the story 
        follows Asta, a young boy born without any magic power who is given a rare grimoire that grants 
        him anti-magic abilities. With his fellow mages from the Black Bulls, Asta plans to become the next Wizard King.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/black clover.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Hunter x Hunter</name>
        <description>The show centers around Gon Freecss, a 12-year-old boy who goes on an adventure 
        to become a Hunter in hopes of finding his father. The Hunters Association holds an annual exam 
        to determine if applicants are worthy of a Hunter's license which is for elite humans with extraordinary abilities.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/hunter x hunter.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Kaguya-sama: Love is War</name>
        <description>The proudly privileged top two students of an elite school each makes it their mission to be the
         first to extract a confession of love from the other. Shuchiin Academy is home to students from Japan's most 
         successful and wealthy families, as well the nation's most brilliant young scholars.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/love is war.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>My Hero Academia</name>
        <description>A superhero-admiring boy enrolls in a prestigious hero academy and learns
         what it really means to be a hero, after the strongest superhero grants him his own powers.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/my hero academia.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>My Dress-Up Darling</name>
        <description>A loner boy and a flashy girl find common ground via cosplay in this sweet and 
        spicy romcom! Wakana has cosplay to thank for many things, but as it turns out, he's not alone.
         When he and Marin meet crossplayer Amane at an event, their new friend shares his story about finding himself through cosplay!</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/my dress up darling.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Chainsaw Man</name>
        <description>Chainsaw Man follows the story of Denji, an impoverished teenager who makes a 
        contract that fuses his body with that of a dog-like Devil named Pochita, granting him the ability 
        to transform parts of his body into chainsaws.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/chainsaw man.png</location>
    </anime>


    <anime>
        <name>Naruto</name>
        <description>It tells the story of Naruto Uzumaki, a young ninja who seeks recognition 
        from his peers and dreams of becoming the Hokage, the leader of his village</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/naruto.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Slam Dunk</name>
        <description>The story follows Hanamichi Sakuragi, who falls in love with a girl named Haruko Akagi, 
        and decides to enter the Shohoku High School Basketball Team in order to attract her, as she is 
        already in love with another Shohoku player, Kaede Rukawa.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/slamdunk.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Bleach</name>
        <description>High school student Ichigo Kurosaki, who has the ability to see ghosts, gains soul 
        reaper powers from Rukia Kuchiki and sets out to save the world from "Hollows".</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/bleach.png</location>
    </anime>

    <anime>
        <name>Dragon Ball</name>
        <description>Dragon Ball tells the tale of a young warrior by the name of Son Goku, a young 
        peculiar boy with a tail who embarks on a quest to become stronger and learns of the Dragon Balls, 
        when, once all 7 are gathered, grant any wish of choice.</description>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/catalog-image/dragonball.png</location>
    </anime>
</catalog>