<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<figures>
    

    <figure>
        <name>Luffy Gear 5</name>
        <price>₱ 683</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>One Piece</anime>
        <sales>1004</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! LUFFY GEAR 5.png</location>
        <description>Monkey D. Luffy is determined to become the Pirate King by finding Gol D. Roger's legendary treasure. Complete your scurvy crew by adding this Pop! Luffy Gear Five to your One Piece collection! There’s a 1 in 6 chance you may find the glow-in-the-dark chase of Pop! Luffy Gear Five. Vinyl figure is approximately 5.35-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>16</stock>
    </figure>


    <figure>
        <name>Katakuri</name>
        <price>₱ 683</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>One Piece</anime>
        <sales>300</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! KATAKURI BOX.png</location>
        <description>Set sail with Charlotte Katakuri, one of the three fearsome Sweet Commanders of the Big Mom Pirates! Expand your One Piece collection by adding Pop! Katakuri to your scurvy crew! Vinyl figure is approximately 4.05-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>10</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>Rorono Zoro</name>
        <price>₱ 853</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>One Piece</anime>
        <sales>903</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! RORONOA ZORO (GLOW).png</location>
        <description>Roronoa Zoro is a swordsman and ex-bounty hunter, who is looking to rejoin his crew members. Bring this exclusive, glow-in-the-dark Pop! Roronoa Zoro into your One Piece Straw Hat Pirates collection. Vinyl figure is approximately 4.15-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>17</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>Unif Ver. Marin Kitagawa</name>
        <price>₱ 7750</price>
        <category>PVC</category>
        <anime>My Dress-Up Darling</anime>
        <sales>805</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/uniform ver. marin kitagawa.jpg</location>
        <description>The 1/7 Scale 'Uniform Ver.' Marin Kitagawa Official Statue by Max Factory brings to life the charming character from 'My Dress-Up Darling' with exquisite detail. Marin stands elegantly in her school uniform, capturing her sweet and innocent demeanor. Every aspect of her design, from her delicate pose to the meticulous rendering of her uniform, is crafted with precision. Standing approximately 9 inches tall, this officially licensed statue is a must-have for fans of the series, offering a beautiful and faithful representation of Marin's endearing character. Available for pre-order now, this statue promises to be a delightful addition to any collection.</description>
        <stock>5</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>Sangoro in Wano outfit</name>
        <price>₱ 683</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>One Piece</anime>
        <sales>301</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! SANGORO IN WANO OUTFIT.png</location>
        <description>Help the scurvy crew of the Straw Hat Pirates defeat Kaido with Pop! Sangoro in his Wano outfit! Give this cook a safe place to drop anchor in your One Piece collection. Vinyl figure is approximately 4.6-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>14</stock>
    </figure>

    

    <figure>
        <name>Yuji Itadori</name>
        <price>₱ 853</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>Jujutsu kaisen</anime>
        <sales>703</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! YUJI ITADORI WITH DIVERGENT FISTS (GLOW) BOX.png</location>
        <description>Yuji Itadori is ready to fight alongside his fellow classmates to become the next generation of jujutsu sorcerers. As Sukuna’s vessel, he combines cursed energy with martial art skills to deliver powerful attacks like the Divergent Fists. This exclusive, glow-in-the-dark Pop! Yuji Itadori is looking forward to growing his sorcery and combat skills in your Jujutsu Kaisen collection. Vinyl figure is approximately 4.5 inches tall.</description>
        <stock>12</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>Nezuko Kamado</name>
        <price>₱ 53299</price>
        <category>Resin</category>
        <anime>Demon Slayer</anime>
        <sales>720</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/nezuko.jpg</location>
        <description>Step into the realm of unparalleled craftsmanship with Infinity Studios magnificent creation, crafted from a fusion of Resin, PU, Polystone, and enhanced with LED illumination. In an impressive 1/4 scale, this masterpiece stands majestically at an estimated H60 * D58 * L45cm, commanding attention with its sheer presence.Limited to a mere 199 pieces worldwide, each meticulouslycrafted to perfection, this masterpiece promises to be a prized possession for the discerning collector. Set to embark on its journey in Q1 (March) 2025, secure your opportunity to own a piece of artistry that transcends boundaries and captivates the senses with Infinity Studios unparalleled creation.</description>
        <stock>10</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>Marshall D. Teach</name>
        <price>₱ 9184</price>
        <category>PVC</category>
        <anime>One Piece</anime>    
        <sales>501</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/Teach.jpg</location>
        <description>From the FiguartsZERO [Extra Battle] series comes Marshall D. Teach! The captain of the Blackbeard Pirates and one of the New Four Emperors is recreated in an incredibly impressive three-dimensional form!</description>
        <stock>9</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>Marin Kitagawa</name>
        <price>₱ 14340</price>
        <category>PVC</category>
        <anime>My Dress-Up Darling</anime>
        <sales>205</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/My Dress-Up Darling.jpg</location>
        <description>From the hit anime series 'My Dress Up Darling' comes Marine Kitagawa </description>
        <stock>0</stock>
    </figure>

    

    <figure>
        <name>Parade Chika Fujiwara</name>
        <price>₱ 1750</price>
        <category>PVC</category>
        <anime>Kaguya-sama: Love is War</anime>
        <sales>407</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/Pop Up Parade Chika Fujiwara.jpg</location>
        <description>From the anime series 'Kaguya-sama: Love is War?' comes a POP UP PARADE figure of the student council secretary of Shuchiin Academy, Chika Fujiwara! Kaguya has been captured in figure form in a lively pose.</description>
        <stock>20</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>Nakano Nino Marine</name>
        <price>₱ 792</price>
        <category>PVC</category>
        <anime>Quintessential Quintuplets</anime>
        <sales>254</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/Nakano Nino Marine.jpg</location>
        <description>Be captivated by the stunning Nakano Nino Marine Look ver. figure from The Quintessential Quintuplets Specials Trio-Try-iT! With intricate details and a vibrant color palette, this figure perfectly captures Nino's charm. A must-have for any fan, this figure brings the beloved character to life and adds a touch of elegance to any collection.</description>
        <stock>11</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>Monkey D. Luffy Gear 4</name>
        <price>₱ 3845</price>
        <category>PVC</category>
        <anime>One Piece</anime>
        <sales>504</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/gear four.jpg</location>
        <description>Banpresto brings us the new One Piece World Figure Colosseum 3 Super Master Stars Monkey D. Luffy Gear 4 figure! This version of the character features a two-dimensional drawing look.</description>
        <stock>11</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>DABI WITH FLAMES</name>
        <price>₱ 688</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>My Hero Academia</anime>
        <sales>100</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! DABI WITH FLAMES BOX.png</location>
        <description>The elder brother of Shoto Todoroki, Toya Todoroki, has joined the League of Villains as a means of achieving vengeance against their father, Pro Hero Endeavor. As Dabi, Toya Todoroki has risen to become a powerful, flame-wielding villain, aiding the League of Villains in their plans to eliminate the top-ranking Pro Hero, All Might. This plan extends to attacking U.A. High School in attempt to end the </description>
        <stock>15</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>Black Asta</name>
        <price>₱ 1000</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>Black Clover</anime>
        <sales>658</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! BLACK ASTA (GLOW).png</location>
        <description>In his quest to become the next Wizard King, Pop! Asta has harnessed demonic power! Wield your magic alongside this Royal Knight of the Clover Kingdoms Black Bulls when you welcome this exclusive, glow-in-the-dark Pop! Black Asta into your into your Black Clover collection! Vinyl figure is approximately 4.55-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>7</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>FATGUM (SLIM FORM)</name>
        <price>₱ 688</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>My Hero Academia</anime>
        <sales>151</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! FATGUM (SLIM FORM) box.png</location>
        <description>Heat up your My Hero Academia collection with Pop! Fatgum (Skinny Form). Pop! Fatgum looks ready to use his strength to fight to the finish. Fatgum is the Pro Hero name of Taishiro Toyomitsu. Add Pop! Fatgum to help the heroes-in-training in your My Hero Academia collection. Vinyl figure is approximately 4.89-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>14</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>YUNO WITH SPIRIT OF ZEPHYR</name>
        <price>₱ 980</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>Black Clover</anime>
        <sales>676</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! YUNO WITH SPIRIT OF ZEPHYR (GLOW) box.png</location>
        <description>Arriving from the outskirts of the Clover Kingdom is Pop! Yuno. This exclusive, glow-in-the-dark Pop! Yuno has summoned Wind Magic to create the Spirit of Zephyr sword. Save your magic and jump on the chance to complete your Black Clover collection with Pop! Yuno with Spirit of Zephyr! Vinyl figure is approximately 4.8-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>9</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>YAMI</name>
        <price>₱ 860</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>Black Clover</anime>
        <sales>302</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! YAMI no box.png</location>
        <description>Arriving from the outskirts of the Clover Kingdom is Pop! Yami. Strengthen your team with one of the most powerful Magic Knights, the Captain of the Black Bulls! Save your magic and jump on the chance to complete your Black Clover collection with Pop! Yami! Vinyl figure is approximately 4.8-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>13</stock>
    </figure>

     <figure>
        <name>GON FREECSS (FISHING)</name>
        <price>₱ 1100</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>Hunter x Hunter</anime>
        <sales>910</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! GON FREECSS (FISHING) box.png</location>
        <description>Embark on a journey with Pop! Gon Freecss as he searches for his father, Ging, and strives to become a skilled Hunter! Complete your Hunter X Hunter set by reeling in this exclusive, fishing Pop! Gon Freecss to your collection. Vinyl figure is approximately 4.35-inches tall</description>
        <stock>5</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>KILLUA ZOLDYCK WITH YO-YO</name>
        <price>₱ 700</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>Hunter x Hunter</anime>
        <sales>1000</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! KILLUA ZOLDYCK WITH YO-YO box.png</location>
        <description>Killua runs away from his family to become a hunter instead of following the family tradition of becoming an assassin. Assemble your Hunter X Hunter collection with the exclusive Pop! Killua Zoldyck with yo-yo. Vinyl figure is approximately 3.75-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>15</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>SHIZUKU WITH BLINKY</name>
        <price>₱ 500</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>Hunter x Hunter</anime>
        <sales>100</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! SHIZUKU WITH BLINKY.png</location>
        <description>Assemble the Phantom Troupe with Pop! Shizuku with Blinky! This 8th member of the troupe will make for a powerful asset in your Hunter X Hunter collection. Vinyl figure is approximately 3.65-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>15</stock>
    </figure>

    <figure>
        <name>NOELLE WITH VALKYRIE ARMOR</name>
        <price>₱ 650</price>
        <category>Funko Pop</category>
        <anime>Black Clover</anime>
        <sales>514</sales>
        <location>http://localhost/action-figure/products-images/POP! NOELLE WITH VALKYRIE ARMOR (DIAMOND) box.png</location>
        <description>Arriving from the heart of the Clover Kingdom is Pop! Noelle. This exclusive, Diamond Collection Pop! Noelle has summoned Water Creation Magic, creating her own suit of Valkyrie Armor! Save your magic and jump on the chance to complete your Black Clover collection with Pop! Noelle with Valkyrie Armor! Vinyl figure is approximately 5.05-inches tall.</description>
        <stock>11</stock>
    </figure>
    
<figure><name>FUMIKAGE TOKOYAMI</name><price>₱ 500</price><category>Funko Pop</category><anime>My Hero Academia</anime><sales>5</sales><location>../products-images/POP! FUMIKAGE TOKOYAMI.png</location><description>Tokoyami harnesses his super move Black Adyss for this exclusive Pop! figure. Add one of U.A. High School’s class 1-A students to your ranks of heroes-in-training. Think twice about leaving Tokoyami in the dark in your My Hero Academia collection. Vinyl figure is approximately 4.25-inches tall</description><stock>15</stock></figure><figure><name>Ventus Studio Luffy vs Kaido</name><price>₱ 44000</price><category>Resin</category><anime>One Piece</anime><sales>1</sales><location>../products-images/93EEEDC8-2AAE-41D6-8B3D-080C6FE728EF.jpg</location><description>The Ventus Studio One Piece Kaido vs. Luffy Resin Statue (Deluxe Version) captures the epic clash from the Wano Arc with stunning detail. Luffy is depicted in Gear Fourth: Snakeman form, ready to unleash his 'Black Mamba' attack, featuring vibrant colors and dynamic smoke effects. Opposing him, Kaido stands in his formidable human-dragon hybrid form, roaring with his colossal kanabo poised to strike, showcasing intricate scales and traditional Wano attire. The base recreates the fiery Onigashima battlefield with rubble, flames, and a stormy sky backdrop, intensifying the scene. Crafted from premium resin and standing approximately 24 inches tall, this statue is a must-have centerpiece for any 'One Piece' fan, embodying the legendary confrontation's raw power and excitement.</description><stock>9</stock></figure><figure><name>Dream Studio Doflamingo</name><price>₱ 14500</price><category>Resin</category><anime>One Piece</anime><sales>1</sales><location>../products-images/dof6.jpg</location><description>The One Piece Dream Studio Doflamingo Resin Statue captures the essence of the infamous Warlord, Donquixote Doflamingo, with meticulous craftsmanship. Depicted mid-action in his iconic pink feathered coat, sunglasses, and confident smirk, Doflamingo's dynamic pose showcases his razor-sharp string manipulation power. The statue's base reflects the treacherous environment of Dressrosa, complete with rubble and debris, and features elements of his Birdcage technique for added intensity. Standing approximately 20 inches tall, this high-quality, hand-painted resin statue is a must-have centerpiece for any 'One Piece' fan, embodying the menacing presence and flamboyant style of one of the series' most iconic villains.</description><stock>14</stock></figure><figure><name>Surge Studio Gaara of the Sand</name><price>₱ 35000</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Naruto</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/gg02.jpg</location><description>The Naruto Surge Studio Gaara of the Sand Resin Statue captures the stoic yet powerful demeanor of the Fifth Kazekage with exquisite detail. Gaara is depicted in a dynamic pose, surrounded by his iconic sand, ready to defend his village with unwavering determination. Every aspect of his character is faithfully recreated, from his distinctive gourd to the intricate patterns on his clothing. The base of the statue features desert terrain, enhancing the character's connection to his homeland. Standing approximately 24 inches tall, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have for any Naruto fan, embodying the strength and resilience of one of the series' most beloved characters.</description><stock>10</stock></figure><figure><name>Burning Ventus Studio Jiraiya</name><price>₱ 32500</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Naruto</anime><sales>1</sales><location>../products-images/j2.jpg</location><description>The Naruto Burning Ventus Studio Jiraiya Resin Statue captures the legendary Sannin in a moment of intense determination and power. Jiraiya is depicted mid-action, summoning the immense flames of his Rasengan, his iconic scroll unfurled beside him. The intricate details of his attire, including his flowing white hair and the vibrant colors of his robes, are faithfully reproduced. The base of the statue features swirling flames, adding to the dynamic energy of the scene. Standing approximately 22 inches tall, this meticulously crafted resin statue is a testament to the indomitable spirit and strength of one of Naruto's most beloved characters.</description><stock>11</stock></figure><figure><name>Gamabunta</name><price>₱ 7500</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Naruto</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/IMG_9222.jpg</location><description>The Naruto Gamabunta Resin Statue by Burning Ventus Studio showcases the awe-inspiring presence of the mighty toad boss summoned by Naruto Uzumaki in times of need. This intricately designed statue depicts Gamabunta in all his colossal glory, towering over the battlefield with commanding authority. His fierce expression and imposing stance exude power and strength, capturing the essence of this legendary creature. Crafted with meticulous attention to detail, from the texture of his skin to the intricate patterns on his armor, this hand-painted resin statue stands as a remarkable tribute to one of Naruto's most iconic summonings. Standing approximately 24 inches tall, this statue is a must-have centerpiece for any Naruto fan, immortalizing the legendary Gamabunta in all his majestic splendor.</description><stock>5</stock></figure><figure><name>YOYO Studio Pain</name><price>₱ 30750</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Naruto</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/image_62f25765-7dc6-44a2-b236-05c69a1adf09.jpg</location><description>The Naruto YOYO Studio Pain Resin Statue encapsulates the enigmatic presence of the powerful Akatsuki leader, Pain. This meticulously crafted statue portrays Pain in his imposing Six Paths of Pain form, radiating an aura of both mystery and menace. Every detail, from his intricate piercings to the Rinnegan eyes that pierce through his cloak, is faithfully recreated with precision. Standing atop a base that echoes the devastation wrought by his powerful abilities, this hand-painted resin statue stands approximately 18 inches tall. A testament to the formidable nature of one of Naruto's most iconic antagonists, this statue is a must-have for any collector seeking to capture the essence of Pain's undeniable impact on the series.</description><stock>25</stock></figure><figure><name>ZBC Studio White Ape Goku</name><price>₱ 39600</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Dragon Ball</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/zb1.jpg</location><description>The Dragon Ball ZBC Studio White Ape Goku Resin Statue brings to life an iconic transformation of the legendary Saiyan warrior. This meticulously crafted statue depicts Goku in his imposing Great Ape form, towering over the battlefield with raw power and ferocity. Every detail, from his massive muscular build to the fierce expression on his face, is captured with stunning accuracy. The dynamic pose and intricate sculpting make this statue a captivating centerpiece for any Dragon Ball collection. Standing approximately 20 inches tall, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have for fans looking to commemorate Goku's epic battles and transformations.</description><stock>20</stock></figure><figure><name>Super Sayian 3 Goku</name><price>₱ 67000</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Dragon Ball</anime><sales>22</sales><location>../products-images/goku12.jpg</location><description>The Dragon Ball Last Sleep Studio Super Saiyan 3 Goku Resin Statue immortalizes one of Goku's most iconic transformations with breathtaking detail. Capturing the essence of his Super Saiyan 3 form, Goku is depicted with his signature long golden hair flowing dramatically as he channels immense power. The intensity of his expression and the dynamic pose convey the sheer force of his energy. Standing approximately 18 inches tall, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have for any Dragon Ball enthusiast, serving as a striking tribute to Goku's indomitable spirit and legendary battles.</description><stock>10</stock></figure><figure><name>Light Weapon Studio Frieza</name><price>₱ 18250</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Dragon Ball</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/IMG_9473.jpg</location><description>The Dragon Ball Light Weapon Studio Frieza Resin Statue captures the tyrannical essence of one of the series' most iconic villains. Crafted with meticulous attention to detail, Frieza is depicted in his menacing final form, exuding an aura of power and malevolence. Every aspect of his character, from his sleek, purple and white armor to his sinister smirk, is faithfully recreated. Standing approximately 12 inches tall on a custom-designed base, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have for any Dragon Ball collector, serving as a chilling reminder of Frieza's formidable presence in the series.</description><stock>5</stock></figure><figure><name>Kuchiki Byakuya</name><price>₱ 21500</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Bleach</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/IMG_0032.jpg</location><description>The Bleach Kuchiki Byakuya Resin Statue by Yuan Meng Studio captures the elegance and power of the esteemed Shinigami captain. Standing tall with a stoic demeanor, Byakuya is depicted in his traditional captain's attire, exuding an air of nobility and authority. Every detail, from the intricate patterns on his haori to the determined expression on his face, is meticulously sculpted with precision. Standing approximately 18 inches tall on a custom-designed base featuring cherry blossom petals, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have for any Bleach fan, serving as a timeless homage to one of the series' most beloved characters.</description><stock>10</stock></figure><figure><name>Flyleaf Studio Ichigo Kurosaki</name><price>₱ 37000</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Bleach</anime><sales>1</sales><location>../products-images/image_40e4e913-b12f-4f38-8db6-c0f914692e25.jpg</location><description>The Bleach Flyleaf Studio Ichigo Kurosaki Resin Statue captures the essence of the determined Soul Reaper with stunning detail. Standing tall in his iconic Bankai form, Ichigo radiates power and resolve as he wields his massive Zanpakuto, Zangetsu. Every aspect of his character, from his determined expression to the intricate design of his cloak and sword, is faithfully recreated with meticulous craftsmanship. Standing approximately 20 inches tall on a custom-designed base evoking the spirit of the Soul Society, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have centerpiece for any Bleach enthusiast, embodying the spirit of Ichigo's relentless quest for justice and power.</description><stock>9</stock></figure><figure><name>Shogun Studios Kenpachi Zaraki</name><price>₱ 29450</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Bleach</anime><sales>3</sales><location>../products-images/image_afb0ed21-2292-4f59-8f31-4d0ed28956da.jpg</location><description>The Bleach Shogun Studios Kenpachi Zaraki Resin Statue captures the ferocious spirit of the enigmatic Soul Reaper captain. Towering with unmatched strength and intensity, Kenpachi stands ready for battle, his imposing figure adorned in his iconic eyepatch and tattered captain's cloak. Every detail, from the rugged texture of his clothing to the wild mane of his hair, is meticulously sculpted to perfection. Standing approximately 24 inches tall on a custom-designed base reminiscent of the Soul Society, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have centerpiece for any Bleach aficionado, epitomizing the raw power and unyielding determination of one of the series' most formidable characters.</description><stock>10</stock></figure><figure><name>Three Artisan Studio Isaac Netero</name><price>₱ 60000</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Hunter x Hunter</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/netero1.jpg</location><description>The Bleach Shogun Studios Kenpachi Zaraki Resin Statue captures the ferocious spirit of the enigmatic Soul Reaper captain. Towering with unmatched strength and intensity, Kenpachi stands ready for battle, his imposing figure adorned in his iconic eyepatch and tattered captain's cloak. Every detail, from the rugged texture of his clothing to the wild mane of his hair, is meticulously sculpted to perfection. Standing approximately 24 inches tall on a custom-designed base reminiscent of the Soul Society, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have centerpiece for any Bleach aficionado, epitomizing the raw power and unyielding determination of one of the series' most formidable characters.</description><stock>8</stock></figure><figure><name>YU Studio Hisoka Phantom Troupe</name><price>₱ 12500</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Hunter x Hunter</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/his2.jpg</location><description>The HxH YU Studio Hisoka Phantom Troupe Resonance Series Resin Statue captures the enigmatic allure of the cunning and unpredictable Hisoka. Standing tall with a devilish grin, Hisoka emanates an aura of danger and excitement, his intricate costume and flamboyant appearance faithfully recreated in stunning detail. Every aspect of his character, from the mischievous twinkle in his eye to the intricate design of his playing cards, is meticulously sculpted with precision. Standing approximately 18 inches tall on a custom-designed base inspired by the dark and mysterious world of the Phantom Troupe, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have for any Hunter x Hunter fan, embodying the captivating charm and formidable presence of one of the series' most intriguing characters.</description><stock>8</stock></figure><figure><name>Niren Studio Geto Suguru</name><price>₱ 32500</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Jujutsu Kaisen</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/IMG-7895.jpg</location><description>The 'Jujutsu Kaisen - Niren Studio Geto Suguru' statue encapsulates the sinister aura of the enigmatic sorcerer from the hit anime series. Crafted with meticulous attention to detail, Geto Suguru is depicted in a dynamic pose, emanating an air of menace and power. Every aspect of his design, from his intricate robes to the piercing gaze of his eyes, is faithfully recreated with stunning accuracy. Standing approximately 12 inches tall on a custom-designed base, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have for any Jujutsu Kaisen fan, capturing the essence of one of the series' most captivating characters.</description><stock>10</stock></figure><figure><name>LY Studio Nanami Kento</name><price>₱ 32750</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Jujutsu Kaisen</anime><sales>1</sales><location>../products-images/image_2a20ebc5-9cdf-472d-9038-3630e58b8d5a.jpg</location><description>The 'Jujutsu Kaisen - LY Studio Nanami Kento' statue epitomizes the stoic strength of the formidable sorcerer from the popular anime series. Crafted with meticulous precision, Nanami Kento stands tall in his signature attire, exuding a sense of calm resolve and unwavering determination. Every detail, from the sharp lines of his suit to the focused intensity of his gaze, is meticulously sculpted to perfection. Standing approximately 10 inches tall on a custom-designed base, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have for any Jujutsu Kaisen enthusiast, capturing the essence of one of the series' most compelling characters.</description><stock>9</stock></figure><figure><name>T.P.A Studios Gojo Satoru</name><price>₱ 16450</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Jujutsu Kaisen</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/IMG_4685.jpg</location><description>The 'Jujutsu Kaisen - T.P.A Studios Gojo Satoru' statue encapsulates the unparalleled power and charisma of the revered sorcerer from the acclaimed anime series. Crafted with meticulous attention to detail, Gojo Satoru stands in a dynamic pose, radiating an aura of unmatched confidence and strength. Every aspect of his design, from the iconic blindfold covering his eyes to the flowing scarf and intricate details of his attire, is faithfully recreated with stunning accuracy. Standing approximately 12 inches tall on a custom-designed base, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have centerpiece for any Jujutsu Kaisen fan, capturing the essence of one of the series' most beloved characters.</description><stock>20</stock></figure><figure><name>Ling Yu Studio Todo Aoi</name><price>₱ 16750</price><category>Resin</category><anime>Jujutsu Kaisen</anime><sales>0</sales><location>../products-images/image_f70fc023-5b68-430f-b983-2580c7c5c0d6.jpg</location><description>The 'Jujutsu Kaisen - Ling Yu Studio Todo Aoi' statue embodies the indomitable presence of the fearsome sorcerer from the hit anime series. Meticulously crafted, Todo Aoi is depicted in a commanding stance, exuding strength and determination. Every detail, from the intricate design of his clothing to the intensity of his expression, is captured with remarkable precision. Standing approximately 10 inches tall on a custom-designed base, this hand-painted resin statue is a must-have for any Jujutsu Kaisen enthusiast, capturing the essence of one of the series' most memorable characters.</description><stock>15</stock></figure><figure><name>HAWKS (FLOCKED)</name><price>₱ 860</price><category>Funko Pop</category><anime>My Hero Academia</anime><sales>1</sales><location>../products-images/POP! HAWKS (FLOCKED) box.png</location><description>Take your My Hero Academia collection to new heights with the exclusive, flocked Pop! Hawks. Hawks, also known as Keigo Takami, is fast and skillful, rising to the highest Pro Hero ranks. With his signature red wings, Hawks looks ready to fly into action. Add Pop! Hawks to help the heroes-in-training in your My Hero Academia collection. Vinyl figure with built in stand is approximately 5.66-inches tall. Find more Funko products on Chalice Collectibles.</description><stock>9</stock></figure></figures>
